Marcelo Leite Junior

Information Systems Final-years Student

Graduating in Information Systems, proactive software developer with 2 years experience in developing services for law firms and teaching programming to university undergrads and technician students. Looking to improve my technical, management and leadership skills, as well to add value and get experience in foreign companies.

Experience

2019-2020 Java Fullstack Developer

SHR Associated Lawyers

Expense guides Automation, Webscrapping and Data Science

2018-2020 Programming Teacher

IFSULDEMINAS - Machado

Java, Python, Github and Data Structure at extension courses

2019 Backend Developer

Regional Milk Producers Cooperative of Serrania, MG (CORPLES)

Java, Springboot, MySQL, React and React Native techs

Certifications

2019 Se	elenium with Java – I	Basics to Advance	t + Frameworks
---------	-----------------------	-------------------	----------------

Udemy - 56 hours

2018-2019 GoStack Bootcamp - Node.js / React / React Native

Rocketseat Educational - Project Based

2018 TOELF ITP – Test of English as a Foreign Language

ID 109104 - 560 points (B2)

2018 Java Programming Masterclass for Software Developers

Udemy – 80 hours

2018 Python 3 COMPLETE – From beginner to Advanced

Udemy - 10 hours

2018 II Technology Security Weekend

Technology College of Ourinhos, SP (FATEC - SP) - 10 hours

Education

2018-2021 Bachelor in Information Systems, IFSULDEMINAS

Expected to graduate in 2021

8.44 CORA (G.P.A)

Favorite fields of study: Technical Programming Language, Data Structure,

Software Quality, Software Engineering

Achievements: Orally Presented a Statistics and Technology Work at the 8th Post Graduation Symposium – Inconfidentes, MG; All years Monitor and Manager of Programming Subjects and Study Groups; Programming Competition Participant of ICPC Regionals 2019 and 10th OLIP;

Personal Info

Address

10 Coronel Jacinto Street Machado, MG 37750-000 Brazil

Phone

+55 35 991006198

E-mail

mleitejunior@gmail.com

Github

github.com/mleitejunior

Languages

Brazilian Portuguese

• • •

Native

English

Advanced

Spanish

Elementary

Skills

Java / Spring Boot Maven / Selenium

MySQL / Postgres Firebase

••••

Node.js / React React Native

PHP / Apache

HTML5 / CSS3 / JS

Python / C++

Agile Scrum

REST

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$